<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Harpo Coin on Harpo</title><link>https://harpocoin.xyz/</link><description>Recent content in Harpo Coin on Harpo</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 14:09:10 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://harpocoin.xyz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Data Model</title><link>https://harpocoin.xyz/blockchain/model/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 04:58:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://harpocoin.xyz/blockchain/model/</guid><description>As its name suggests, the Blockchain is a set of blocks roughly organized as a chain. Ideally, every block would be neatly lined up and form a single linked list.
Block A block has the following properties:
a hash value that serves as its unique identifier. Hash values are considered unique as long as they refer to different content a reference to the previous block as a field prev_hash These two values are enough for linking the blocks.</description></item><item><title>Stages</title><link>https://harpocoin.xyz/chainsync/stages/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 11:58:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://harpocoin.xyz/chainsync/stages/</guid><description>ChainSync: CS
Purpose of ChainSync CS Download and process blocks from peers Synchronize the blockchain Update chain state Stages CS starts when node boots and stops when the node stops CS is normally is mode CS_FOLLOW CS starts in CS_INIT If the chain is too far behind the current tip, CS switches to CS_SYNC CS_INIT Tip is set to last known best, or latest checkpoint or genesis block CS_SYNC Indicates that our node is too far behind and should quickly download and sync up Sync relies on a &amp;ldquo;torrent&amp;rdquo; like download mechanism Mode is entered when the median of the height of the peers is farther than 1 block from tip, for 30 seconds Mode is exited when at the end of the sync process, node is no longer in the above situation CS_FOLLOW Receives blocks through Gossip protocol and process them</description></item><item><title>Game</title><link>https://harpocoin.xyz/blockchain/game/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 05:23:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://harpocoin.xyz/blockchain/game/</guid><description>In this game, we receive blocks one by one. Our goal is to determine if the block is valid and if yes, where it should be placed in the &amp;ldquo;blockchain tree&amp;rdquo;. The bonus goal is to keep track of the longest chain, i.e. the main chain.
Branch and chain are used interchangeably here.
A branch is the series of blocks going from a leaf (a block that has no follower) to the first block</description></item><item><title>Sync Mode</title><link>https://harpocoin.xyz/chainsync/sync/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 12:21:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://harpocoin.xyz/chainsync/sync/</guid><description>State Peers PeerId Listen address Hash, Height Peer Leader: Peer that has the highest height, only peer we request headers from Headers Headers are requested sequentially from Leader Response headers begin in DETACHED state Chain Fragment Header State List of headers received from GetHeaders DETACHED: headers have hash but no height, not validated and not connected to blockchain PARTIAL_LINKED: prev_hash links with hash of previous header.</description></item><item><title>Block Sync</title><link>https://harpocoin.xyz/chainsync/block_sync/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 13:36:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://harpocoin.xyz/chainsync/block_sync/</guid><description>Notes Follow bittorrent principles a block = a piece we only download from peers we don&amp;rsquo;t choke peers TODO: Study the BitTorrent protocol
Block Validation Check merkle root Check transaction zk proofs nullifiers auth signature</description></item><item><title>Open letter</title><link>https://harpocoin.xyz/grant-response/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://harpocoin.xyz/grant-response/</guid><description>I’m reaching out because I’d like to strongly encourage you to submit a grant proposal to cover ongoing development and maintenance of Ywallet. I will support your proposal and do my best to get the other committee members to support and approve it as well. Many of them have already commented on what a great wallet Ywallet is.
Thanks for reaching out. There are a few reasons why I don&amp;rsquo;t plan to submit a grant proposal, even though I have done so in the past for other projects.</description></item></channel></rss>